<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Suraj Nayak</title><link>/</link><description>Recent content on Suraj Nayak</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>Copyright © 2008–2019, Steve Francia and the Hugo Authors; all rights reserved.</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 09:37:09 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Show Your Work</title><link>/posts/first-post/</link><pubDate>Sat, 22 May 2021 09:37:09 +0530</pubDate><guid>/posts/first-post/</guid><description>Books play an important role in a person’s life in many ways. Some books change people’s lives, some give us a healthy lifestyle and some heal the soul.
Showing your work is a personal manifesto on how to get creative work done. Austin Kleon explains the perspective on doing the work you love. The book is full of quotes with impactful ideas. Before starting any work, we should think about ideas thoroughly.</description></item><item><title>Suraj Nayak</title><link>/about/</link><pubDate>Fri, 14 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/about/</guid><description>I am from a village in Hebri, located in the coastal area. I am currently studying computer science engineering in N.M.A.M.Institute of Technology. I am a self-motivated individual and I am passionate about technology, learning new things, and solving problems effectively. I am dedicated to my job and punctual with my time. In leisure time, I read books and play cricket.</description></item><item><title>Computer Graphics</title><link>/posts/third/</link><pubDate>Wed, 12 May 2021 12:09:13 +0530</pubDate><guid>/posts/third/</guid><description>Computer graphics is a field of computer science that studies methods for digitally synthesizing and manipulating visual and geometric information using computational techniques. Although the term often refers to the study of three-dimensional computer graphics, it also encompasses two-dimensional graphics and image processing.
There are many applications of computer graphics like:
Print design Digital art Special effects Video games Visual effects Computer-aided design and many more OpenGL is a cross-language, cross-platform application programming interface for rendering 2D and 3D vector graphics.</description></item><item><title/><link>/posts/archives/</link><pubDate>Tue, 28 May 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>/posts/archives/</guid><description/></item></channel></rss>